skoola.com 2016-08-03

# Privacy Policy

##  PRIVACY POLICY 

[www.skoola.com](http://www.skoola.com/) is registered at 1st Floor Waterfront Plaza, 12 Admiralty Way, Lekki Phase 1, Lagos, NIGERIA.

Skoola.com takes the privacy of its user's data very seriously. Please read the following policy to understand how we will treat your personal data when you use our site. In the event of any changes to this Policy, all visitors to our site will be notified via our homepage forthwith. Please be assured that we will only use your data as specified here for our legitimate business purposes.

When do we collect data? 

We can collect data on you from a variety of different sources including: 

When you become a subscriber

When you purchase products or services from the site;

When you speak to our customer services personnel;

Via explicit data capture measures, for example by entering competitions and completing surveys and;

Via implicit data capture measures such as studying the pages you read the most and the use of cookies. 

In any of the above cases the data we collect could be personal data. 

What do we do with your personal information?

When you register to become a user on our website, we may need to collect information about you which may be necessary to providing the services you expect in the best possible way. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, and your address. 

Unless we have your express consent we will only disclose personal data to third parties if this is required for the purpose of completing your transaction with us. This is of course subject to the proviso that we may disclose your data to certain permitted third parties, such as members of our own group, our own professional advisers who are bound by confidentiality codes, and when we are legally obliged to disclose your data. 

By becoming a subscriber you consent to receive from us by e-mail, our e-newsletter and details of other special offers and services which we may consider to be potential interest to you. 

Skoola.com retains and uses your personal information to provide you with the best online study search experience by providing you with a personalised service and to give you details of services which we think will be of interest to you. We may also use the information to process any transactions you undertake with us and for internal administration and analysis. 

We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your express consent. 

Cookies

Cookies are small files which are sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. If you have registered with skoola.com, then your computer will store an identifying code in the cookie which means you do not need to type in your email address each time you return to the site. Other than this, we do not store your password or any other information in the cookie, or use it for any other purpose. Our third-party advertiser may place or recognise a unique cookie on your browser. 

Consent

By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by skoola.com in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. Some information and e-mails sent to skoola.com may be used as testimonials but no e-mail address or contact details will be displayed. 

Change/Modify Details

To change your membership details please log in to My Account. You can change your e-mail address or password using the Manage Your Account Details feature 

Contact

If you have any questions or concerns about the information we hold about you, you can contact us by emailing ask@skoola.com
